Guide to the Johan Kugelberg punk collection, circa 1974-1986.
Kugelberg, Johan punk collection
- Series I. Magazines and Fanzines
  - Shews, 1977; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Editors: Peekay, Plucky
  - Show-Kai, 1991; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Publication location: Madison, WI, United States
    Editors: David Public, Betsy Bath
    Notes: Cover title: Show; full title and number from introduction
  - Sick Teen, 1994-1996?; Issue #: 58 fuckin' millionth ish (Box 6, Folder 21)
    Publication location: Green Bay, WI, United States
    Editors: Rev. Norb
    Notes: Cover title: (Sic) Teen
  - Sick Teen, 1989?; Issue #: Super Uncool (2)4 ish (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Situation 3, 1977? (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Editors: Loft
    Notes: "if you thought the last issue was crap…" cover. FACSIMILE: color photocopy.
  - Ska Special, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Editors: Lionel Young
  - Skate Punk, June, 1982; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 4 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Editors: Steve Caballero
  - Skate Punk, November, 1981; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Publication location: [San Jose, CA?], United States
  - Skatecore, 1983?; Issue #: 5 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Editors: Steven Eye
  - Small Axe, 1977-1980; Issue #: 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Editors: Ray Hurford
  - Small Axe, 1981-1982?; Issue #: 9-13 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Smart Verbal, 1981; Issue #: 5-6 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Birmingham, Great Britain
    Editors: Boz, Mo, Zo
    Notes: Contributions from Martin Atkins
  - Smegma Journal, 1979?; Issue #: 4-5 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Publication location: Maumee, Ohio, United States
    Editors: Barry Henssler
  - Sniffin' Glue (Box 34)
  - Sounds On Campus, 1965-1968? (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Notes: 8 center pages from an unknown issue of a fanzine, likely Sounds on Campus but possibly Mod Magazine, containing an essay by Danny Fields.
  - Spurt, 1977-1978?; Issue #: 2-4 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Haymarket [Sydney], New South Wales, Australia
    Editors: Ian Hartley
  - Stab Your Back, June, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Editors: Sarapata
  - Stabmental, 1979-1980; Issue #: 2-5 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Publication location: Haddenham, Buckinghamshire/Thame, Oxfordshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Tom Craig, John Balance (Geoff Rushton)
  - Stand and Deliver, 1981?; Issue #: 3/4 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Editors: John Dingwall
    Notes: Double issue
  - Start!, 1981?; Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Publication location: Bristol, Great Britain
    Editors: Pete Cunliffe
  - Stercus, 1977?; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    Publication location: [Canada?]
    Editors: G. Zus
  - Stop!, March-August, 1982; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    Editors: J.D. King, John Holmstrom
  - Stop!, December, 1982-1984; Issue #: 5-9 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Story So Far, The, 1980-Fall; Issue #: 4 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Editors: Tim Marts
  - Stranded (UK), 1977?; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Publication location: Exeter, Devonshire, Great Britain
    Editors: John Jacques
  - Strange Things are Happening, 1988-1990; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1, 3, 4, 6-7 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    Publication location: St. Albans, Hertsfordshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Brian Hogg, Richard Noris, Phil Smee
  - Strangled, April, 1977; Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Editors: T. Moon, P. Jac
  - Street, January, 2004; Issue #: 149 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Publication location: Street, Tokyo
    Notes: Japanese street style magazine. Special issue on New York and London.
  - Street Life (US), 1977; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1-2 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Editors: Bob Morris
  - Street Press, 1971-1973; Issue #: 3-4, 6-7, 9 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Notes: Cover title: Birmingham Street Press
  - Street Press, April, 1971; Issue #: 2 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Stringent Measures, 1981; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Publication location: Warwickshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Chris Coleman
  - Sub/Pop, November, 1980; Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Editors: Bruce Pavitt
    Notes: Hand-colored in crayon. Cover title: Subterranean Pop.
  - Sub/Pop, 1982; Issue #: 8 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Notes: Hand-colored in crayon.
  - Subliminal Tattoos, 1995-Fall; Issue #: 6 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    Editors: Robert Dupree
  - Substitute, 1978; Issue #: 1 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Publication location: National City, CA, United States
    Editors: Tom Griswold, Jacki Ramirez
  - Suburban Press, 1970-1972; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Editors: Jeremy Brook, Jamie Reid, Nigel Edwards
    Notes: Photocopied facsimile.
  - Suburban Relapse, 1983; Issue #: 9 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    Publication location: N. Miami, FL, United States
    Editors: Barry Soltz
  - Subvert, 1983; Issue #: [5] (Box 6, Folder 51)
    Editors: Richard Jevons
  - Suicide Alley, April, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Dorrington, Queensland, Australia
  - Sunset Gun, 1982? (Box 6, Folder 52)
    Publication location: Glasgow, UK, Great Britain
    Editors: Klark Kent
  - Super Boss Rock/Pop Lust, 1982-Winter; Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    Editors: Rob Morgan
    Notes: Split zine, tete-beche
  - Super Rock, August, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Superdope, 1991-1997?; Issue #: 1-8 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Publication location: San Francisco, CA/Seattle, WA, United States
    Editors: Jay Hinman
    Notes: Includes printout of "Supderdope 1.0," the first installment of this zine's electronic successor.
  - Surfin' Bird, 1979; Issue #: 3 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    Publication location: Verdun, Quebec, CA, Canada
    Editors: Danny Allman
  - Swellsville, 1989/1990-Winter; Issue #: 9 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    Editors: Jack Thompson
  - Synopsis Magazine, 1980; Issue #: 2 (Box 6, Folder 58)
    Publication location: Plymouth, Great Britain
    Editors: David N. Tarafder
  - Tales from Dr. Feelgood, 19785? (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - TB Sheets, March, 1978; Issue #: 8 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Publication location: Temple City, CA, United States
    Editors: Bob Stremel
  - Tear It Up, 1980? (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Publication location: Kilwinning, Ayrshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Janette Anderson, David Belcher, Kenneth Bergeron, E. W. Musgrave
  - Teen Looch, 1995?; Issue #: 8 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    Publication location: Hudson, PA, United States
    Editors: Brian Turner
  - Teenage Rampage, 1975?; Issue #: 0 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    Notes: Unbound (Single sheet)
  - Ten Commandments, 1980; Issue #: 5 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    Editors: Robert Hodgens, Kirsty McNeil, Robert Sharp
  - These Thing's, April, 1977; Issue #: 1C (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Editors: Randy Bollocker
  - Throat Culture, 1990; Issue #: 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Publication location: Union, NJ, United States
    Editors: Rob O'Connor, Jim White, Jon Seidman
    Notes: Flexi disc lacking
  - Thunder Road, 1978; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Publication location: Bogota, NJ/Cypress, CA, United States
    Editors: Steve Pond, Phil Ceccola
  - Tidal Wave, 1980?; [2?] (Box 7, Folder 9)
    Editors: Tem
  - Titanium Exposé, 1998-1999; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Editors: Christopher Kalani Woo
  - Toffee Sunday Smash!, 1987-Summer; Issue #: 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Editors: John Hanrattie
  - Top Rankin', 1978?; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    Publication location: Havertown, PA, United States
    Editors: Walt Taylor
  - Top Rankin', 1979-1980; Issue #: 2-3 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Top Rankin', 1982; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 5 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Toranna Punks, 1977-1980? (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Trans-Oceanic Trouser Press, October, 1974; Issue #: 5 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Editors: Ira Robins, Karen Rose, Dave Schulps
  - Trans-Oceanic Trouser Press, 1976; Issue #: 13 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Editors: Ira Robbins
    Notes: Continues as Trouser Press
  - Trouser Press, June, 1976; Issue #: 14 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Notes: Continued from Trans-Oceanic Trouser Press
  - Trouser Press, Volume #: 3, Issue #: 15 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Trouser Press, February, 1977; Issue #: 18 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Trouser Press, March, 1982; Issue #: 71 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    Editors: Ira Robbins, Scott Isler
  - Trouser Press, November, 1982; Issue #: 79 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Trouser Press, April, 1981; Volume #: 8, Issue #: 80 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Twisted, July 1977-March 1978; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    Editors: R. Roberts
  - Ugly Things, 1993-1997; Issue #: 12-15 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    Editors: Mike Stax, Johan Kugelberg
  - Ugly Things, 1998-2000; Issue #: 16-18 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    Notes: CD lacking
  - Ugly Things, 2001-2002; Issue #: 19-20 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Ugly Things, 2003-2004; Issue #: 21-22 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Ugly Things, 2005-2006; Issue #: 23-24 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Ugly Things, 2007-2008; Issue #: 25-26 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    Publication location: La Mesa, CA, United States
  - Ugly Things, 2008-2009; Issue #: 27-28 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Ugly Things, 2009-2010; Issue #: 29-30 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    Editors: Mike Stax
  - Unhinged, 1990-Spring; Issue #: 6 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    Publication location: Wiltshire, Great Britain
  - Useless Information, February, May, 1977; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1-2 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    Publication location: St. Petersburg, FL, United States
    Editors: Dennis Dalcin
  - Vague, 1980, 1982-1983; Issue #: 7, 11-15 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Publication location: Boscome, Bournesmouth, Great Britain
    Editors: Tom Vague
  - Vague, 1986-1989; Issue #: 18-20, 22 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    Publication location: Mere, Wiltshire, Great Britain
  - Vague, 1980-1981; Issue #: 8-10 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Vague, 1980; Issue #: 3, 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Publication location: North Salisbury, Wiltshire/Boscombe, Bournemouth/Mere, Wiltshire/London, UK, Great Britain
  - Varulven, 1972-1981; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 4-7 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    Editors: Joseph Allen Viglione
    Notes: Includes press release "Varulven Proudly Presents the Count" and "Count Viglione" fliers.
  - Vertical Urge, November,1985; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    Editors: Sergie Loobkoff
  - Vintage Violence, 1977-1978; Issue #: 2, 4-5 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    Publication location: Silver Spring, MD, United States
    Editors: Mike Heath (Live Wire)
  - Vortex, 1977; Issue #: 1 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    Publication location: [Chiswick?], Great Britain
    Editors: Dee Dee Tee, Billy Horgan, John Morris, Toni, Jimmy Frenscch
  - Walkerpeople, 1996; Issue #: 64 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Wasteland, November, 1977?; Issue #: 1, 3 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Waxpaper, Volume #: 4, Issue #: 6 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    Publication location: [United States?]
    Editors: Gene Sculatti, Joe Robinson
  - Waxpaper, August 26, 1977; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 9 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - We Are All Prostitutes, 1980? (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Publication location: [Bristol, UK?], Great Britain
    Editors: The Pop Group
    Notes: Contents are political rather than musical, but probably released in conjunction with the Pop Group's 1980 single of the same name. Inscribed "Hello from the Pop Group."
  - We Got Power, 1982?; Issue #: 5 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Publication location: Santa Monica, CA, United States
    Editors: Jordan Schwartz
  - We Got Power, 1982?; Issue #: Yearbook '82 [1-4] (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Notes: Issues #1-4 bound together with tape, with an added cover.
  - Weird NJ, 1998; Issue #: 10 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Publication location: Bloomfield, NJ, United States
    Editors: Mark Sceurman, Mark Moran
  - West Indian Music Appreciation Society, 1972-1974? (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Publication location: Berkhamsted, Hertsfordshire, Great Britain
    Notes: 7 Issues
  - White Stuff, March-December, 1977; Issue #: 2, 4-6 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Why Mildred Skis, June, 1989-March, 1991; Issue #: 5-7 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    Editors: Frank Kogan
    Notes: Alternate cover title: Wear Mildred Sheets
  - Wild Dog, 1979; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 1-3 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Publication location: Houston, TX, United States
    Editors: Sluggo
  - Wimmin of Bimbox, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    Publication location: Michigan/Toronto, United States/Canada
    Editors: Johnny Noxzema
    Notes: "Limited edition - 1990 Michigan Womyn's Music Festival"
  - Windmills and Psychedelic Dreams, 1981? (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Editors: Paper Alcohol Collective
  - Wool City Rocker, 1981; Issue #: 14 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    Publication location: West Yorkshire, UK, Great Britain
    Editors: Nick Toczek
  - Woolly Bugger, 1996-Summer; Issue #: 4 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Publication location: [Seattle, WA?], United States
    Editors: Jeff Fuccillo
  - Wrong Image, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Xiphoid Process, 1981; Issue #: 6 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    Editors: Control Rat X
    Notes: Includes manuscript note from one of the authors/editors.
  - Xpert I, 1979; Issue #: 5 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    Editors: Amrik Rai, Garry Millward, Robert Wood
    Notes: Mimeographed-- risk of fading. A4 interior with 8.5 x 13 cover; stored upside due to cover fold at bottom edge.
  - XS, March-August, 1983; Issue #: 1-3 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    Publication location: Whitwick, Leicestershire, Great Britain
    Notes: pp. 52-64 lacking
  - Y, 1981?; Issue #: 4 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    Publication location: Keyworth, Nottingham, Great Britain
    Editors: Matthew Collin, Steve Willet, Jon Tait
    Notes: Mail art publication.
  - Yet Another Fanzine, 1991; Volume #: 2, Issue #: 1 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    Editors: C. Koon
  - Young, Fast, and Scientific, 1978-1979; Issue #: 1-2 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Yourflesh Quarterly, 1998; Issue #: 38 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    Editors: Cindy Jaeger, Peter Davis
  - Zeppelin, 1973-1974; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 2, 5, 7, 10 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    Publication location: Unites States
    Editors: Edward Richards, Fred Toetdman
  - Zigzag, October, 1969-July, 1970; Issue #: 6-7, 11-13 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    Publication location: Luton, Bedfordshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Pete Frame, Ian Mann
  - Zigzag, October, 1970-1971; Issue #: 16-21 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    Publication location: North Marston, Buckinghamshire, Great Britain
    Notes: Jamie Reid artwork throughout the issue.
  - Zigzag, 1971-March, 1973; Issue #: 22-29 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    Editors: Pete Frame, John Tobler, Ian Mann
  - Zigzag, 1973; Issue #: 30-31 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Editors: Pete Frame, John Tobler
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 3 no. 7
  - Zigzag, 1973-1974; Issue #: 33, 36-39 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    Editors: Connor McKnight, John Tobler
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 3 no. 9-12, Vol 4. 1 no. 2
  - Zigzag, 1974; Issue #: 40-47 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    Editors: Connor McKnight, John Tobler, Pete Frame, Andy Childs
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 4 no. 3, Vol. 5 no1-7
  - Zigzag, December, 1974-April, 1975; Issue #: 48-51 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Editors: Andy Childs
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 5 no. 8-9
  - Zigzag, July-August, 1975; Issue #: 54-56 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 6 no. 4-6. 3 8.5x14 pamphlets and one loose 8.5x14 sheet in a single folder
  - Zigzag, 1975-1976; Issue #: 57-62, 64 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    Editors: Pete Frame, John Tobler, Andy Childs
    Notes: Alt. numbering: Vol. 6 no. 7
  - Zigzag, 1976-February, 1977; Issue #: 65-69 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Zigzag, May-July, 1974; Issue #: 72-74 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    Editors: Paul Kendall
  - Zigzag, 1977; Issue #: 77-78 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    Publication location: Leighton Buzzard, Bedforshire, Great Britain
    Editors: Kris Needs
    Notes: Cover title: Birmingham Street Press. With bookseller's description of a the present issues of this periodical.
  - Zigzag, 1978-1979; Issue #: 84, 91-93 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Zigzag, 1979-1980; Issue #: 94-97 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Zigzag, 1980; Issue #: 99-100 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    Notes: Advertising supplement laid in.
  - Zigzag, 1980; Issue #: 105-106 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Zigzag, 1980-1982; Issue #: 107, 109, 111, 115, 126 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Zigzag, 1984; Volume #: 1, Issue #: 8, 10 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    Editors: Mick Mercer
    Notes: Official Warner Brothers publication.
- Series II. Fliers and Posters
  - Miscellaneous (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous A-L (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Miscellaneous M-Z (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Unknown (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Miscellaneous Unknown (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Framed fliers (Box 31)
  - Framed poster (Box 36)
  - Framed poster (Box 37)
  - Framed poster (Box 38)
  - Framed poster (Box 39)
  - Miscellaneous Posters (Mapcase-folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous French posters (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - [none], ca. 2004-2011; 18 x 17 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Venue: n.p.
    Location: [New York]
    Additional bands or artists: [Green Day]
    Main text: Crowd surfing and moshing is not advised
    Notes: Public service poster obtained at a Green Day performance ca. 2000s, warning against the dangers of crowd surfing and moshing. Two sheets of paper held together with black electrical tape.
  - [none], ca. 1970s; 16.5 x 11.5 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Location: [Sweden]
    Main text: Mr SM: är detta kultur?
  - → ↑ → [Tsk tsk tsk], 42 x 30 cm. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Location: Australia?
    Main text: The first EP by → ↑ → is now on sale: Universal Workshop
  - 101'ers, 1975-1976; 18 x 23 in. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    Venue: The Elgin
    Location: [London]
    Main text: The 101'ers r'nb - Rave On! Every Monday Night at the Elgin
    Notes: Poster for Joe Strummer's pre-Clash band The 101'ers.
  - 45 Grave, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Venue: Whisky a Go Go
    Location: Los Angeles, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Sexsick, Minutemen
    Main text: Lust and Irish Catholic guilt - A eulogy for valor - A tangle of minds … Punk rockers sought in beating of girl, 15 … 45 Grave, Sexsick, Minutemen May 23 at the Whiskey
  - 45 Grave, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Venue: Godzilla's
    Location: Sun Valley, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion
    Main text: 45 Grave, Social Distortion - Godzilla's …
  - 45 Grave, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Artist: M. Sims
    Venue: Cove Theatre and Ichabods
    Location: Hermosa Beach and Fullerton, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Twisted Roots, Christian Death, Pompeii 99
    Main text: 45 Grave - Friday Dec. 3rd, Cove Theatre …
  - 45 Grave, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Venue: The Country Club
    Location: [Los Angeles, CA?]
    Additional bands or artists: Subhumans
    Main text: 45 Grave, Subhumans, at the country Club, thurs. April 22nd
  - 45 Grave, 1984; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Additional bands or artists: Redd Kross, Tex & the Horseheads, D. Boone [of the Minutemen]
    Main text: Are you prepared for… the rapture? A night of music & film that will lift you off of this sin-ridden planet. Featuring: 45 Grave …
  - 45 Grave, 1982; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Artist: D.B.
    Additional bands or artists: Phranc, Levi Dexter, The Tribe
    Main text: 45 Grave with Phranc - Plus… Levi Dexter and the Tribe!
  - 45 Grave, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Additional bands or artists: Outer Circle, Salvation Army, Sex Sick, Minutemen
    Main text: 45 Grave - Fri. May 21 - 9 + 11 PM - with Outer Circle …
  - 999, 1985; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Artist: B. Otis
    Venue: Santa Monica Civic Aditorium
    Location: Santa Monica, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Social Distortion, D.I.
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents 999 - Nine-Nine-Nine - Social Distortion - and DI - former Adolescents … Hey son lookie - "999" just like da good old days! Can I go with ya? We can pogo an we …
  - 999, 1980s; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    Venue: Florentine Gardens
    Location: Hollywood, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Circle Jerks, Wasted Youth
    Main text: 999, Circle Jerks, Wasted Youth
  - A.4, 1981; 17 x 24 in. (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Venue: Paradiso
    Location: [Amsterdam], Netherlands
    Additional bands or artists: Holland's Glorie, Vopo's, Playmobilz
    Main text: Pakjes Punk - A.4, Hollands Glorie, Vopo's & Playmobilz - Wie Heeft Mijn Laars Gejat?
  - Adicts, The, 1984; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Olympic Auditorium
    Additional bands or artists: Toy Dolls, Effigies, Negative Approach
    Main text: Maximum fun! At another exclusive Goldenvoice U.K. double-header
  - Adolescents, The, 1981; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: Starwood
    Additional bands or artists: Eddie & the Subtitles, 45 Grave
    Main text: Adolescents, Eddie & the Subtitles, 45 Grave - Starwood Tuesday Feb 10
  - Agent Orange, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Music Machine
    Main text: Agent Orange - Music machie May 24
  - Agent Orange, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: The Barn
    Location: [Vermont?]
    Additional bands or artists: Salvation Army, Godhead, Rhino 39, Red Alert
    Main text: Groovy haps! Agent orange…
  - Agression, 1980s; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Ronnie's
    Location: Monrovia, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Insolents, Doggy Style, Heavy Dirt
    Main text: Wed. April 2: Agression - Insolents
  - Angelic Upstarts, 1985; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Otis & Biscuits, Olyumpic Auditorium, and London Exchange
    Location: Beverly Hills, Los Angeles, and Costa Mesa, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Wasted Youth, SSD Control
    Main text: Angelic Upstarts; LA's Wasted Youth with SSD Control
  - Angry Samoans, The, 1981; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: The Vex
    Additional bands or artists: TSOL, Middle Class, Rim Pests, Rayonics, Escapees, The Hated, Funeral, Shattered, China White, Middle Men, Deadskins
    Main text: Wed. 4/29 - The Angry Samoans
  - Anti-Nowhere League, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Perkin's Palace
    Location: Pasadena, CA
    Additional bands or artists: Social Unrest
    Main text: Goldenvoice Present Anti-Nowhere League
  - Anti-Nowhere League, 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Venue: Perkin's Palace, Santa Monica Civic Center
    Additional bands or artists: Charged GBH, Crass
    Main text: Goldenvoice presents in the coming months - British Invasion
  - Anti-Pop (record label), ca. 1979; A4 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    Location: [UK]
    Additional bands or artists: Wavis O'Shave, Arthur 2-Stroke, The Noise Toys
    Main text: Wavis O'Shave, Arthur 2-Stroke, The Noise Toys - Out now on Anti-Pop
    Notes: General promotional flier for Anti-Pop's releases in and around 1979.
  - Avengers, 1978; 11 x 17 in. (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Venue: Masque
    Additional bands or artists: Dils, Suicide, Liars, F-Word
    Main text: Avengers - Dils - Suicide!
  - B-52's, 7.25 x 10 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Live House Taku-Taku
    Location: Kyoto, Japan
    Main text: The B-52's modern dance & plastic muzik show
  - Back From the Grave [compilation series], ca. 1985; 31 x 21.75 in. (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Artist: [Mort Todd]
    Main text: Hey bud! Get these albums!
    Notes: INSCRIBED by BFTG cover artist Mort Todd: "Hail / Cesar! / Beast Regards ~ Mort Todd '66 [i.e. '86?]". Record store poster for the first five volumes of the '60s punk compilation series Back From the Grave.
  - Bad Brains, 1981; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: Botony Rocks
    Location: New York
    Additional bands or artists: Nastyfacts
    Main text: Friday-Saturday January 16-17 - Bad Brains
  - Bad Religion, 1982; 8.5 x 11 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    Venue: S.F. Music Works
    Location: San Francisco
    Additional bands or artists: Short Dogs Grow, Tunnel Creeps, Jon T.
    Main text: This isn't art this is suicide… Bad Religion
  - Bad Religion, 1983; 8.5 x 5.5 in. (Box 9, Folder 16)